1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/RSVP"))
9. refresh()
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Create RSVP Alert Header"), "Create RSVP Alert")
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"))
21. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Choosen users filtered"), 2)
41. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Done button"))
45. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Template selection button"))
49. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP template with given value"))
53. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
57. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-14")
61. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Send button"))
65. waitForPageLoad(2)
69. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-14")