1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Survey-Quizz-Poll"))
9. click(findTestObject("Survey/New Survey btn"))
13. check(findTestObject("Survey/Poll radio btn"))
17. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Survey/Poll radio btn"), 1)
21. click(findTestObject("Survey/More btn"))
25. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
29. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Survey title"), "TC-31")
33. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 input"), "Choose image with mountains")
37. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 Answer 1 input field"), "Picture 1")
41. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add image Q1(a1)"))
45. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/first image on a server"))
49. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 answer 2 input field"), "Picture 2")
53. click(findTestObject("Survey/add image Q1(a2)"))
57. click(findTestObject("Survey/6th image from server TC-31"))
61. delay(30)
65. click(findTestObject("Survey/Send btn Survey"))
69. click(findTestObject("Survey/Poll tab"))
73. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-31")
77. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-31")