1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Left-hand menu_RSVP"))
5. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP templates tab"))
9. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/New Template RSVP"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP template title"), "TC-13")
17. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body iframe"), 1)
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body"), "Hello! This is automated RSVP template from Katalon")
25. switchToDefaultContent()
29. setText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 1 title input"), "What is your favorite movie?")
33. setText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Answer 1 input"), "Harry Potter")
37. setText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Answer 2 input"), "Kill Bill")
41. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 2 switch"), 2)
45. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 2 switch"), 2)
49. check(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 2 switch"))
53. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 2 switch"), 1)
57. setText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Question 2 title input"), "Why?")
61. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP template Save button"))
65. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP templates tab"))
69. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-13")
73. delay(2)
77. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Filtered RSVP template"), "TC-13")
81. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
85. click(findTestObject("Templates Action menu/Preview Template Action"))
89. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview alert iframe"), 2)
93. takeFullPageScreenshot([])
97. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/close alert preview"))
101. switchToDefaultContent()
105. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
109. click(findTestObject("Templates Action menu/Edit Template Action"))
113. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Create RSVP Alert Header"), 2)
117. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create RSVP/Create RSVP Alert Header"), "Edit RSVP template")
121. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP template Save button"), 2)
125. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP template Save button"))
129. click(findTestObject("Create RSVP/RSVP templates tab"))
133. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-13")
137. delay(2)
141. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered Template"), "TC-13")