1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose Alert Button"))
5. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), 2)
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), "Create Pop-up Alert")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-1")
25. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body iframe"), 2)
29. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body"), "Hello! This is automated alert from Katalon")
33. switchToDefaultContent()
37. delay(3)
41. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Send button"))
45. waitForPageLoad(2)
49. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-1")
53. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-1")
57. delay(5)
61. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
65. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stop-Start alert"))
69. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stopped status"), 2)