3. Open Publisher page on a dashboard
9. Click Policies on the left-hand menu
15. Click add policies button
21. Enter policy name
25. check(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Pop-up checkbox"))
29. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Pop-up checkbox"), 2)
33. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Policy Save btn"), 2)
39. Save policy
43. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"))
49. Verify if Policy exist
53. delay(5)
57. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Publishers/filtered publisher"), "RestrictedAccess")
63. Click on Actions menu
69. Select Edit
73. check(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Wallpapers checkbox"))
77. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Wallpapers checkbox"), 2)
81. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Policy Save btn"), 2)
87. Save policy
91. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"))
97. Verify if Policy exist
101. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
105. click(findTestObject("Publishers/Policies/Duplicate Policies"))