1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Left-hand menu Surveys-Quizz-Poll"))
5. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"))
9. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey template btn"))
13. check(findTestObject("Survey/Quizz radio btn"))
17. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Survey/Quizz radio btn"), 1)
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-32")
25. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 input"), "If you freeze water, what do you get?")
29. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 Answer 1 input field"), "coffee")
33. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 answer 2 input field"), "ice")
37. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct"))
41. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add question btn"))
45. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 input"), "At what temperature does water change its state?")
49. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Survey/choice options"), 1)
53. click(findTestObject("Survey/choice options"))
57. click(findTestObject("Survey/Multiple choice"))
61. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 1 input field"), "0")
65. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 2 input field"), "50")
69. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add option"))
73. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 3 input field"), "100")
77. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct Q2(a1)"))
81. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct Q2(a3)"))
85. click(findTestObject("Survey/Save survey template btn"))
89. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"), 3)
93. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"))
97. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-32")
101. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-32")
105. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
109. click(findTestObject("Templates Action menu/Preview Template Action"))
113. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview alert iframe"), 2)
117. takeFullPageScreenshot([])
121. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/close alert preview"))
125. switchToDefaultContent()
129. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
133. click(findTestObject("Templates Action menu/Edit Template Action"))
137. click(findTestObject("Survey/Save survey template btn"))
141. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"), 3)
145. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"))
149. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
153. click(findTestObject("Templates Action menu/Create alert using this template"))
157. click(findTestObject("Survey/More btn"))
161. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
165. click(findTestObject("Survey/Send btn Survey"))
169. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-32")
173. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-32")