1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Screensavers"))
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Lockscreen/Create Lockscreen header"), "Create Screensaver")
13. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/more"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-42")
25. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Screensavers/Upload screensaver area"), 2)
29. uploadFileWithDragAndDrop(findTestObject("Screensavers/Upload screensaver area"), "C:\Users\Home\git\Katalon\Imagesfortest\icecity.jpg")
33. delay(5)
37. getAttribute(findTestObject("Screensavers/uploaded screensaver file"), "src")
41. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Save wallpaper button"))
45. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Draft tab"))
49. waitForPageLoad(2)
53. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-42")
57. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-42")