1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose Alert Button"))
5. refresh()
9. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), 2)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), "Create Pop-up Alert")
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"))
21. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
41. waitForPageLoad(2)
45. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Template selection button"))
49. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Template with given name"))
53. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"))