1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Wallpapers"))
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Create Wallpaper Header"), "Create Wallpaper")
13. refresh()
17. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/more"))
21. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Choosen users filtered"), 2)
41. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
45. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-16")
49. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Upload wallpaper area"), 2)
53. uploadFileWithDragAndDrop(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Upload wallpaper area"), "C:\Users\Home\git\Katalon\Imagesfortest\rocks.png")
57. delay(90)
61. getAttribute(findTestObject("Wallpapers/uploaded wallpaper file"), "src")