1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose Alert Button"))
5. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), 2)
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), "Create Pop-up Alert")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-1")
25. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body iframe"), 2)
29. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body"), "Hello! This is automated alert from Katalon")
33. switchToDefaultContent()
37. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Send button"))
41. waitForPageLoad(2)
45. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-1")
49. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-1")
53. delay(5)
57. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
61. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stop-Start alert"))
65. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stopped status"), 2)
69. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
73. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stop-Start alert"))
77. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Disributing status"), 2)
81. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
85. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/View graph"))
89. takeElementScreenshot(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/View graph image"))
93. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/view graph close btn"))
97. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
101. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Preview in actions menu"))
105. takeFullPageScreenshot([])
109. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview alert iframe"), 2)
113. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/close alert preview"))
117. switchToDefaultContent()
121. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
125. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Duplicate alert"))
129. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
133. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "Duplicate pop-up alert")
137. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Send button"))
141. waitForPageLoad(5)
145. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-1")
149. waitForPageLoad(5)
153. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"), 2)
157. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
161. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/resend alert from actions menu"), 2)
165. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/resend alert from actions menu"))
169. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Resend btn"))
173. sendKeys(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
177. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-1")
181. verifyElementClickable(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Select all checkbox"))
185. check(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Select all checkbox"))
189. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Select all checkbox"), 1)