1. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
5. click(findTestObject("Survey/Create alert using this template"))
9. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
13. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-33")
17. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 input"), "value", "If you freeze water, what do you get?", 0)
21. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 Answer 1 input field"), "value", "coffee", 0)
25. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 answer 2 input field"), "value", "ice", 0)
29. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 input"), "value", "At what temperature does water change its state?", 0)
33. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 1 input field"), "value", "0", 0)
37. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 2 input field"), "value", "50", 0)
41. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 3 input field"), "value", "100", 0)
45. click(findTestObject("Survey/Send btn Survey"))
49. click(findTestObject("Survey/quizz tab"))