1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Left-hand menu Surveys-Quizz-Poll"))
5. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"))
9. click(findTestObject("Survey/Survey template btn"))
13. check(findTestObject("Survey/Quizz radio btn"))
17. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Survey/Quizz radio btn"), 1)
21. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Survey title"), "TC-32")
25. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 input"), "If you freeze water, what do you get?")
29. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 Answer 1 input field"), "coffee")
33. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 answer 2 input field"), "ice")
37. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct"))
41. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add question btn"))
45. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 input"), "At what temperature does water change its state?")
49. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Survey/choice options"), 1)
53. click(findTestObject("Survey/choice options"))
57. click(findTestObject("Survey/Multiple choice"))
61. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 1 input field"), "0")
65. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 2 input field"), "50")
69. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add option"))
73. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 answer 3 input field"), "100")
77. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct Q2(a1)"))
81. click(findTestObject("Survey/Mark as correct Q2(a3)"))
85. click(findTestObject("Survey/Save survey template btn"))
89. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Survey/Survey templates tab"), 3)