1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Survey-Quizz-Poll"))
9. check(findTestObject("Survey/Classic survey radio button"))
13. click(findTestObject("Survey/More btn"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Survey title"), "TC-25")
25. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 input"), "Are you satisfied with our services?")
29. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 Answer 1 input field"), "Yes")
33. setText(findTestObject("Survey/Q1 answer 2 input field"), "No")
37. click(findTestObject("Survey/Add question btn"))
41. click(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 delete btn"))
45. verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Survey/Q2 delete btn"), 2)
49. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Skin choice button"))
53. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Skin with given index"))
57. sendKeys(findTestObject("Survey/alert width"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
61. setText(findTestObject("Survey/alert width"), "400")
65. sendKeys(findTestObject("Survey/alert height"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
69. setText(findTestObject("Survey/alert height"), "500")
73. click(findTestObject("Survey/Preview Survey btn"))
77. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview alert iframe"), 2)
81. takeFullPageScreenshot()
85. switchToDefaultContent()
89. click(findTestObject("Survey/Send btn Survey"))
93. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-25")
97. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Filtered sent alert"), "TC-25")
101. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Actions menu check"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
5. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stop-Start alert"))
9. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stopped status"), 2)
13. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
17. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Stop-Start alert"))
21. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Disributing status"), 2)
25. click(findTestObject("Survey/3dots Actions"))
29. click(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/View graph"))
33. takeElementScreenshot(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/View graph image"))