1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Login Test Cases/Login with Valid Credentials"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://dadebug.commclouds.com/Demo/admin/auth")
9. waitForPageLoad(3)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Login Page/DAlogo"), 2)
21. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Login Page/Version number"), 2)
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Login Page/Version number"), "Version: 11.4.0.1 (stage/11)")
29. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/Login input field"), "Zoya")
33. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/Password input field"), "tzH6RvlfSTg=")
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/button_Log in"))
41. delay(4)
45. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/h1_Dashboard"), 4)
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose Alert Button"))
9. refresh()
13. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), 2)
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Create Pop-up Alert header"), "Create Pop-up Alert")
21. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"))
25. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
29. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ", CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
37. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
41. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Choosen users filtered"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
45. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
49. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-6")
53. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body iframe"), 2)
57. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert body"), "Hello! This is automated alert with preview check from Katalon")
61. switchToDefaultContent()
65. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Skin choice button"))
69. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Skin with given index"))
73. check(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Acknowledgement checkbox"))
77. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Acknowledgement checkbox"), 2)
81. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Add print button"), 2)
85. check(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Add print button"))
89. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alerts settings right-hand menu/Add print button"), 2)
93. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/More button"), 2)
97. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview button"), 4)
101. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview button"), 3)
105. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview button"))
109. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Preview alert iframe"), 2)
113. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/print button"), 1)
117. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Postpone time selection"), 1)
121. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Postpone button"), 1)
125. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Creation Date"), 1)
129. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Alert Title Preview"), 1)
133. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Alert logo Preview"))
137. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Preview/Acknowledgement OK button"))
141. switchToDefaultContent()
145. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Save Button"))