1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Lockscreens"))
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Lockscreen/Create Lockscreen header"), "Create Lockscreen")
13. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/more"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
29. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
33. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-24")
41. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Upload wallpaper area"), 2)
45. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Select image from server button"))
49. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/first image on a server"))
53. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Wallpapers/uploaded wallpaper file"), 1)
57. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Send wallpaper button"))
61. waitForPageLoad(2)
65. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-24")