1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Video Alerts"))
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Create Wallpaper Header"), "Create Video Alert")
13. click(findTestObject("Video Alert/Videoalert more btn"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-46")
25. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Video Alert/Videoalert upload area"), 2)
29. click(findTestObject("Video Alert/Select video from the server"))
33. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Select image from server button"))
37. click(findTestObject("Video alerts/First video from the server"))
41. delay(1)
45. getAttribute(findTestObject("Video alerts/uploaded video file"), "src")
49. click(findTestObject("Video alerts/Video alert description"))
53. setText(findTestObject("Video alerts/Video alert description"), "Hello! This is automated video alert from Katalon")
57. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Send wallpaper button"))
61. waitForPageLoad(2)
65. setText(findTestObject("Pop-up Alerts page/Search by title field"), "TC-46")