1. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Video Alerts"))
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Create Wallpaper Header"), "Create Video Alert")
13. click(findTestObject("Video Alert/Videoalert more btn"))
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Built-in test cases/Choose recipients"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
13. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
17. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
21. sendKeys(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), Keys.chord(CONTROL, "a", BACK_SPACE))
25. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "DESKTOP-9UH6GK7 ")
33. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
37. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-47")
25. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Video Alert/Videoalert upload area"), 2)