1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Login Test Cases/Login with Valid Credentials"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://dadebug.commclouds.com/Demo/admin/auth")
9. waitForPageLoad(3)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Login Page/DAlogo"), 2)
21. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Login Page/Version number"), 2)
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Login Page/Version number"), "Version: 11.4.0.1 (stage/11)")
29. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/Login input field"), "Zoya")
33. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/Password input field"), "tzH6RvlfSTg=")
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/button_Log in"))
41. delay(4)
45. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login Page/h1_Dashboard"), 4)
5. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Compose alert button expansion"))
9. click(findTestObject("Dashboard Page/Wallpapers"))
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Create Wallpaper Header"), "Create Wallpaper")
17. refresh()
21. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/more"))
25. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"))
29. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Filter field"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9")
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/All user list-filtered"), "LAPTOP-E6BU4LL9 ")
37. click(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/filtered user selection"))
41. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Choose recipients modal window/Choosen users filtered"), 2)
45. click(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Done"))
49. setText(findTestObject("Create Pop-up Alert Page/Alert Title field"), "TC-17")
53. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Upload wallpaper area"), 2)
57. uploadFileWithDragAndDrop(findTestObject("Wallpapers/Upload wallpaper area"), "C:\Users\Home\git\Katalon\Imagesfortest\future.bmp")
61. delay(90)
65. getAttribute(findTestObject("Wallpapers/uploaded wallpaper file"), "src")